{
    "subject": "resource/Mathnet",
    "predicate": "property/episodenumber",
    "object": "26",
    "human_readable": "Mathnet episode number is 26.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7493463754653931,
            "question": "What is the episode number of Mathnet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5381286144256592,
            "question": "How many episodes are there in Mathnet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3808475136756897,
            "question": "Where can people watch Mathnet episodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35770824551582336,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Mathnet episodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3091907203197479,
            "question": "When was Mathnet first aired?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26749151945114136,
            "question": "Is Mathnet a popular television show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19124354422092438,
            "question": "What genre is Mathnet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16311964392662048,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in Mathnet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11873586475849152,
            "question": "What age group is Mathnet targeted towards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11192663758993149,
            "question": "Does Mathnet feature educational content?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mathnet episode number is 26.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4178_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What age group is Mathnet targeted towards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4178_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the main characters in Mathnet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4178_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Mathnet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4178_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4178_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention any specific episode number for the show Mathnet. Therefore, based on the given information, it cannot be confirmed that there are exactly 26 episodes of Mathnet."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}